 [{
    "Category":"Difficult Wares",
    "Clues": [
      {
        "Question": "Don't bother busting out a calculator, this part of your CPU will handle your calculations",
        "Answer": "Arithmetic Logic Unit (ALU)"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Fortnite players beware, this vehicle handles allows data to communicate between your CPU and memory",
        "Answer": "Data Bus"
      },
      {
        "Question": "It's hard to do a many things at once, but this function of the OS makes sure you don't need to think about it!",
        "Answer": "Multitasking"
      },
      {
        "Question": "It won't be sealing any ducts, but this roll of metal backs up your data in a pinch!",
        "Answer": "Magnetic Tape"
      },
      {
        "Question": "It's the fastest memory in the west...make sure you have some of this to speed up processer instructions for frequently-accessed memory",
        "Answer": "Static RAM (SRAM)"
      },
      
    ]
  },
  {
      "Category":"My Little Program",
      "Clues": [
        {
          "Question": "You won't see letters in your math outside of algebra, unless you use this common number base",
          "Answer": "Hexadecimal"
        },
        {
          "Question": "They say opposites attract, and nowhere is that more true than with this binary operation, where opposites create truth!",
          "Answer": "Exclusive Or (XOR)"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Only your children have access to these types of variables",
          "Answer": "Magnetic Tape"
        },
        {
          "Question": "You might not be able to find your keys because they're somewhere you haven't checked yet...or they could be somewhere you can't SEE, due to this OOP principle",
          "Answer": "Encapsulation"
        },
        
        {
          "Question": "Your program will most certainly crash due to this exception if you try and access something that doesn't exist!",
          "Answer": "Null Pointer Exception"
        },
        
      ]
    },
    {
      "Category":"The Social Network",
      "Clues": [
        {
          "Question": "Hackers won't be able to touch your data if you use this type of secure connection",
          "Answer": "Virtual Private Network (VPN)"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Traffic is a pain when the people in front of you won't move, creating this phenomenon on a network",
          "Answer": "Bottleneck"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Bluetooth is just one type of this sort of network",
          "Answer": "Personal Area Network (PAN) or Piconet"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Your ISP probably didn't lie to you about your bandwidth, but what you're seeing isn't bandwidth, it's this networking term",
          "Answer": "Throughput"
        },
        {
          "Question": "This type of transport method doesn't reach Star Trek levels of speed, but it does utilize this type of cable",
          "Answer": "Fiber Optic (Cable)"
        },
        
      ]
    }
  ]
